The History of Khorinis
Presents
The Bloody Band
You blockhead!
Did you really think, you will escape away with it?
Captain! I beg you! This...
Shut up!
You've lost the right to tell anything, when you've took the royal gold.
Since many years we were comrades.
To think that, such a disgrace was hiding among us.
No! Please! I will explain everything!
Will you explain that? Ha!
You've promised to betray your comrades, to lure our ship into a trap.
All this, in exchange for amnesty for such a miserable rat like you!
I could not believe, when I saw, with who is he talking with, behind a tavern
Dirty nit ...
It's a misunderstanding! Captain, I just wanted to ...
You wanted to scramble out at our cost!
I should drag you for it under the keel! Damn, I'm getting too soft for an old age.
On board with him!
I want to see blood!
This is the end, scumbag!
Please! I beg you! No! Mercy!
We are on the high seas! I won't swim to shore!
Who says, you have to swim?
You can not even afford to face the consequences of your own actions.
You're really lousy sneak.
No...
This is how treacherous dogs ends.
So you did not try to do something you could regret in the History of Khorinis, my friend.
starring:
Greg - Andrzej Tomecki
The accused - Krzysztof Zakrzewski
Young pirate - Hubert Chłopicki
Old sweat pirate - Krzysztof Siwiński
Screenplay - Michał Nowak
Photos and direction - Milosz Duda, Radosław Rak
Production - Piotr Czołnowski
Editing - Miłosz Duda, Radosław Rak, Mateusz Pawlowski
Sound Editing - Szymon Nawrocki
Music - Cezary "Fang" Wnuk
Level design - Krystian Ogonowski
Animations - Maksymilian Łakomy
Substantive help - Mateusz Majda, Bartosz Samburski
English subtitles - Radosław Rak, Bartosz Biały, based on Polish captions by Szymon Żak